Two main choices we need to make
在构建循环神经网络时
when we want to build a recurrent neural network
我们需要做的两个主要选择是
are choosing a cell type, so a long short term memory
选一个 cell 类型 例如长短时记忆 cell
cell or a vanilla RNN cell or a gated recurrent unit cell,
vanilla RNN cell 或门控循环单元 cell
and how deep the model is.
以及模型的深度
How many layers will we stack?
即我们要堆叠多少个层？
And since we'll need word embeddings
而且由于当我们的输入是单词时
if our inputs are words, we'll also
我们将需要单词嵌入
look at embedding dimensionality.
我们还应考虑嵌入维度
In practice, LSTMs and GRUs perform better
在实践中 LSTM 和 GRU 的性能优于
than vanilla RNN.
vanilla RNN
That much is clear.
这一点大家都很明确
So which of the two should you use?
那么 你应使用这两个中的哪一个呢？
While LSTMs seemed to be more commonly used,
虽然 LSTM 似乎更常用
it really depends on the task and the dataset.
但这更多地取决于任务和数据集
Multiple research papers comparing the two
很多对比这两者的研究论文
did not announce a clear winner.
最终都没能给出一个明确的答案
Let's take an example task, character level
我们来看一个示例任务 字符级
language modeling.
语言建模
A great paper titled Visualizing and understanding
一篇名为《可视化和理解你的循环网络》
your recurrent networks compare the two
的优秀论文使用两个不同的数据集
on two different datasets.
比较了这两者
The result on the first dataset saw
第一个数据集的结果表明
GRUs doing better than LSTMs.
GRU 优于 LSTM
Better here being lower across entropy loss
这里的优于指的是在大小不同情况下
when comparing them at different sizes.
交叉熵损失更低
On a different dataset, the two are tied each scoring better
在另一个数据集上 它们两结合在了一起 每个分别在
at different sizes.
不同的大小情况下得分更高
In the text below the video we elaborate more
在视频下的文本中 我们对这个对比
on this comparison.
做了详细说明
But the recommendation here is to try both on your dataset
但我建议在你的数据集和任务上两个都试试
and task and compare.
对比看看
Note that you don't have to test this on your entire dataset.
注意 你不需要在整个数据集上进行测试
You can try it on a random subset of your data.
而是使用你的数据的一个随机子集
Regarding the number of layers, results for character level
对于层数 字符级语言建模的
language modeling show that a depth of at least two
结果显示至少两层的深度
is shown to be beneficial.
较为有益
But increasing it to three actually gives mixed results.
但增加到三实际上会使结果有点混乱
Another task like advanced speech recognition
另一个任务 如高级语音识别
can show improvements with five and even seven layers often
显示在没有 LSTM cell 的情况下 五层甚至七层
without LSTM cells.
会改善结果
In the text below the video, we have
在视频下的文本中 我们
provided a number of example architectures
提供了不同任务的示例架构
for different tasks along with the sizes and number
以及每个示例的层大小
of layers for each example.
和数量
If your RNN will be using words as inputs,
如果你的 RNN 将使用单词作为输入
then you'll need to choose a size for the embedding vector.
那么你需要为嵌入向量选择大小
How do we go about choosing this number?
那么我们该如何选择这个数字呢？
Experimental results reporting a paper
一篇名为《如何生成良好的单词嵌入》的
titled how to generate a good word embedding
论文中的实验结果
show that the performance of some tasks
表明嵌入的大小越大 某些任务
improve the larger we make the embedding,
的性能越高
at least until a size of 200.
大小至少到 200
In other tests, however, only marginal improvements
但在其他测试中 超过 50 的大小
are realized beyond the size of 50.
仅取得了非常小的改进